不不不
No,no,no,no,no!
拜托 我只想正当地谋生
Oh,come on,man! I'm just
trying to make an honest living!
你所做的 哪有正当可言
There's nothing honest
about what you do!
谁供给你迷魂药
Who supplies you with Vertigo?
告诉我 就放你走
Tell me now and you live.
求你了 别杀我
Please! They'll kill me!
不管你是怕谁 你该更怕我
Whoever you fear... Fear me more!
好吧
Okay,okay!
我们叫他伯爵 我只知道这些
We call him The Count,that's all I know.
我发誓
I swear to God!
把我放下来
Get me down from here!
找到你想要的了吗
Find what you're looking for?
解决了三个非法销售迷魂药的 Diggle
Took down three Vertigo
pushers tonight,Diggle.
最后一个可算给出了个名字
Last one finally knew a name.
伯爵
The Count.
伯爵 这名字比帽衫侠还弱
The Count? That's worse than The Hood.
你别再出去了
You're not going back out there.
今晚还没完事
I'm not done for the night.
不管伯爵是谁 他杀人无数
Whoever this Count is,he has
a lot of blood on his hands,
他要还的账可太多
and it is long past
time he started paying.
慢着 你没抓住重点
Well,slow down,I think
you're missing the point here.
什么
What?
Thea
Thea.
她的听证会还有几小时开始
Her hearing's in a few hours.
你觉得她更在乎毒枭落网
You think she cares more about some
drug lord getting his just desserts,
还是在她最需要你时 你的陪伴
or you being by her side
when she needs you the most?
我们该走了
Hey,we should get going.
法官可不吃时髦地迟到这套
Judges don't appreciate the
value in being fashionably late.
还有其他提醒吗
Got any other tips?
你自己别插嘴
Let the lawyer do all the talking.
他们会给你便笺簿和纸
但别在上面玩井字棋
They'll give you a pad and paper
but do not play tic tac toe.
法官也不会欣赏这点的
Judges don't appreciate that,either.
好运啊 飞毛腿
Come on,Speedy.
我知道
I know,I know.
很想起身就走 但不要这样...
Keep on trying to get up
and go,but... just don't.
真希望爸爸在这
I wish dad were here.
我在呢
I'm here.
我们该走了 Thea
We should leave now,Thea.
Queen小姐
Ms. Queen.
Thea 这里 请解释下
Thea,over here. Can we get a comment?
就解释一句
Just one comment!
Thea 你要去戒毒吗
Thea,are you going into rehab?
Queen小姐 你是被Balliol Prep赶跑了吗
Miss Queen,are you being
dispelled from Balliol Prep?
你担心结果吗
Are you worried about the outcome?
诉讼事件表尾号1-10-5-6
人民诉讼Thea Dearden Queen
Docket ending 1-10-5-6,People
vs. Thea Dearden Queen.
非法持有管制药物
Possession of a controlled substance,
服用管制药物后驾驶
driving under the influence
of a controlled substance.
双方律师 我知道你们达成了认罪协议
Counselors,I understand you've
reached a plea agreement.
是的 法官
We have,Your Honor.
鉴于我的委托人未成年
诉讼人同意执行缓刑
Given that my client is a juvenile,the
people have generously agreed to probation.
未成年
Juvenile?
这写着她18了
Says right here she's 18.
她现在是18了 但被捕时
She is 18 now,Your Honor,but
at the time of arrest,
离18岁生日还差两天
she was still two days
shy of her 18th birthday.
Queen小姐没有前科
Ms. Queen has no priors.
Queen小姐的家人为她销了前科
Well,just because Ms. Queen's family
sweeps her priors under the rug,
不代表没有过前科
doesn't mean they don't exist.
你帮你的委托人脱罪
让老板避免处理
You get your client off,and you help
your boss avoid dealing with the drug
席卷城市的毒品问题
that's sweeping across
our city like the plague.
你们双赢 但输的是斯特林市民
Everyone wins,except us,the
people of Starling City.
- 法官大人 出于尊敬...
- Queen小姐 不管你是否喜欢
- Your Honor,with all due respect...
- Ms. Queen,like it or not,
你是这种威胁的代表
you are now the poster
child for this menace.
可能人们看到Queen一家
使用迷魂药 没逃脱法网
Maybe if people see that the Queen
family can't get away with using Vertigo,
他们在使用时会更谨慎思考
they'll think twice
before using it themselves.
认罪协议被否决
The plea arrangement is denied.
案子将进行庭审
This case will proceed to trial.
他们不能这样
They can't do this.
这人不能把我女儿送进监狱
That man cannot send
my daughter to prison.
我们有何选择
What are our options?
进行中间上诉
An interlocutory appeal.
但庭审法官有权拒绝认罪协议
But trial judges have discretion
to reject plea agreements.
我想你该准备接受
I think you might want to prepare
yourself for the possibility
我们不想看到的结果
that this isn't going to go our way.
抱歉 Queen女士
I'm sorry,Mrs. Queen.
我要去为上诉做准备了
I'll get to work on the appeal.
城中最好的刑事辩护律师也不过如此
Well,so much for the best criminal
defense attorney in the city.
Thea 我们会搞定这个的 我保证
Thea,we will handle this,I promise.
就像你向Walter保证你会忠贞于他吗
Like you promised Walter you'd
always stay faithful to him?
- 这让我感觉好多了
- 够了
- I feel better already.
- That's enough!
别担心 听上去你不用再忍我多久了
Don't worry. Sounds like you won't have
to be putting up with me much longer.
她没意识到事情有多严重吗
What,does she not realize
how serious this is?
她嗑药了
She took drugs.
- 还开车 她可能会害死自己或他人
- 我知道
- She drove. She could have killed someone,or herself.
- I know.
那法官只想杀一儆百
All that judge is looking for
is someone to make an example of.
为什么非要是她
What does it have to be her?
也许不是必须
Maybe it doesn't.
听着 我有些事要做
Listen,I have to go do something.
你会没事的 对吗
Are you going to be okay?
可不是我面临牢狱之灾
I'm not the one facing prison.
你现在为他们工作了吗
You working for them now?
你为什么这么对我
Why are you doing this to me?
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
或其他的关系
Or...something.
为什么你要保护我
I mean,why'd you bother keeping me safe
既然你要把我交给他们
if you were just going
to hand me over to them?
把我弄出去
Just get me out of here.
我做不到
I can't.
喂 别把我留在这
Hey! Don't leave me here!
我为了你才回来的
I came back for you!
你听到没
Do you hear me?
我为了你回来的
I came back for you!
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: Ducky 贤狼 骗骗米
校对: 西瓜红和安坠崖
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十二集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 12
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
我来找Hall警官
Hi. Looking for Detective Hall.
他们说他是副警长
I was told he works in Vice.
Oliver
Oliver?
McKenna Hall
McKenna Hall.
我还在找穿廉价西装的中年男子呢
Here I was,expecting a middle
aged guy in a bad suit...
这就是McKenna Hall啊
And I got McKenna Hall.
我常给人惊喜
I live to surprise.
我记得呢
Well,I remember.
那个你害我们被踢出的
俱乐部叫啥来的
What was that club that
you got us kicked out of?
- 帝威俱乐部
- 好吧 我得辩解两句
- The Club Deville?
- Okay,in my defense,
那没有标志特别说 一定要穿好衣服
there was no sign that specifically
said you had to keep your clothes on.
那你是个警察哈
So,a cop?
我猜你不再去参加派对啥的了
I guess you're not hitting
the party circuit anymore.
我还是会去舞会的
I still go to raves.
现在去做卧底
I just go undercover now.
我得穿的稍微多些 藏住徽章和枪
And I have to dress slightly more
appropriately to hide my badge and gun.
没错
Right.
所以你找副警长干啥 Oliver
So what do you need
with a vice cop,Oliver?
迷魂药
Vertigo.
哦对 我在电视上
看到了你妹妹 我很抱歉
Right. I saw your
sister on TV. I'm sorry.
法官想杀一儆百
The judge is trying to
make an example of her.
所以我想 如果我能找到贩毒的人
So I was thinking,if you could
find the person selling the drugs,
也许能为Thea解围
it make take some of the heat off Thea.
说比做容易
Easier said than done.
我做了些调查 得到了个名字
Did some digging and
came up with a name.
伯爵
Um,The Count?
Oliver 几月前我们就知道伯爵了
Oliver,we've known about
The Count for months.
我也希望能有更多信息
但没太多他的资料
I wish this was thicker,but we
really don't have much on him.
希望我们能在你妹妹庭审前抓住他
Love to say we're going to catch
him before your sister's trial,
但不太可能
but it's highly unlikely.
我换岗要迟到了
Oh,I am late for my shift.
那你有他的消息 就告诉我好吗
Well,if you hear of anything
about this guy,just...let me know?
我很欣赏你对妹妹的关心
I always loved how much
you cared about your sister.
但让警察去做本职工作吧
But leave the policing
to the police,okay?
好吧
Okay.
Queen想要什么
What did Queen want?
他是个老朋友 妹妹被抓了
He's an old friend,sister's jammed up.
还有别的事吗 警官
Anything else,Sergeant?
没了
No.
你需要找个裁缝了
You need a tailor.
你也知道那帽衫侠
You know about the hood guy.
他逼我走投无路
He just cornered me,man.
帽衫侠
The hood guy?
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
我知道
Oh,I know.
你没法泄露不知道的事
You can't divulge
secrets you don't know.
但还是要杀鸡儆猴
But... examples must be made.
纯度最高的迷魂药
Vertigo,in its purest form.
直接注入血液时
When injected directly
into the bloodstream,
会影响脑中的丘脑区
it affects the thalamus
region of your brain.
那是你痛觉感受器接收信息之处
Which is where all of the information
from your pain receptors is collected.
你定会处于极度痛苦的
No doubt you're in excruciating pain.
但实际上 不会
But actually,you're not.
你只是觉得如此
You just think you are.
我见过这情况持续多天
直到心脏衰竭
I've seen it last for days,until
finally the heart gives out.
还剩一颗子弹
One bullet left.
你可以将子弹射向我 完成复仇
Now,you can use that bullet to
shoot me and take your revenge,
或者自杀
or...you could shoot yourself.
这是你的选择
It's your choice.
帽衫侠
The Hood.
来找我
Coming for me.
有点意思
Interesting.
我知道你不太喜欢赖床
I'm learning you're not
much of a morning snuggler.
我也知道你不到中午不起床
And I'm learning that you don't like
to wake up at any hour that ends in a.m.
这没错
That's true. Yeah.
要是你白天忙于工作
我夜晚打理夜店
So if you're busy being a lawyer all day
and I'm managing a night club all night,
我们什么时候能见面
when exactly do we
get to see each other?
我去开 你别动
I got it. Stay.
Thea怎样
Hey,how... how is Thea holding up?
她还好 谢谢
She's doing okay. Thank you.
其实我想来找Laurel谈谈
Um...Actually,I... I
came to talk to Laurel.
谢谢你昨天出庭
Thank you for coming to court yesterday.
当然
Yeah,of course.
但我觉得法官不会动摇
But I don't think the judge is
willing to move off his position.
坚定打击犯罪 是他的竞选宣言
Taking a hard line against criminals
is a platform for his reelection.
我想让你和你爸谈谈
I need you to talk to your father.
他在这体系内 而且...
He's inside the system,and...
没准他能说服Brackett法官
maybe he cashes in a
chip with Judge Brackett,
让他放过Thea
gets him off throwing the book at Thea.
Oliver 我不...
Oliver,I don't...
Laurel 我竭尽全力了
Laurel,I am working
on something on my end,
要是...我没有成功 你爸爸这边
能帮到我妹妹的希望最大
but... If it doesn't work out,this
is my best chance to help my sister.
求你了
Please.
我尽量吧
I'll see what I can do.
但是不能保证
But no promises.
谢谢你
Thank you.
门都没有
Absolutely not.
爸 我知道和Oliver不对眼
Dad,I know how you feel about Oliver.
那你怎么还开口求我这事
Then why would you
even ask me to do this.
因为Thea 她只有18岁
Because Thea,she's only 18 years old.
所以她是成人了 就要承担责任教训
Which makes her an adult.
She can take her medicine.
是时候让Queen家族好好反省了
It's about time someone
in the Queen family did.
那Lance一家呢
What about the Lance family?
年轻女孩放浪形骸
不计后果 听着耳熟吗
A young girl acting out,engaging in
reckless behavior,does that sound familiar?
Laurel 别说了
Laurel,don't go there.
Thea 就和我记忆中Sarah一样
Thea,she's just like I remember Sarah.
在我印象中你妹妹不是这样
That is not how I remember your sister.
那是因为你只想记住她好的一面
That's because you remember her
the way that you wish she had been,
而不是真实的那面
not the way that she actually was.
她并没有被你教育成圣人
She's not the Saint that
you make her out to be.
我知道她店铺盗窃被捕
但是你帮她遮掩过去了
I know she was arrested for shoplifting
and I know you made it go away.
也许当时让她坐牢
她就不会到Queen该死的船上去
Well,maybe if I let her go to jail,Queen
wouldn't have had her on that damn boat.
爸 你说的好像她是被绑去的
Dad,you make it sound
like he kidnapped her.
一直以来 我们都将Sarah的死
怪罪于Oliver身上 但Sarah也有错
For so long,you and I have blamed Oliver
for Sarah's death,but Sarah's to blame,too.
当我看着Thea
我就仿佛看到Sarah的影子
When I look at Thea,I see
Sarah's potential in her.
还有她的瑕疵
And her flaws,too.
是的 Thea犯了错
Yes,Thea made a mistake.
但她已经受了很多苦
But she's been through a lot.
她失去了父亲和兄长
She lost a father and a brother.
她需要的不是监狱
She doesn't need prison.
而是帮助 所以求你...
She needs help. So please...
我会打几个电话试试
I'll make some calls.
我在阿富汗就见够了
苏联人留下的鸟文
I've seen a fair amount of Cyrillic back
in Afghanistan left over by the Soviets.
这是俄国人的地方
Is this Russian owned?
这里俄国黑手党在斯特林市
明面意义上的总部
This is the not so hidden headquarters for
the Starling City chapter of the Bratva.
Diggle...不管我说什么
不管发生什么 你都要支持我
Diggle... Whatever I say,whatever
goes down,just go with it.
很高兴再见到你
Zdravstvuyte.
我也是
Good to see you.
许久未见
Long time.
尤其对于黑手党队长来说
Particularly for Bratva captain.
我一直在考虑该投资什么
I was trying to figure out
where to put my interests.
最终决定是药物
I decided on pharmaceuticals.
我说的可不是阿司匹林
I don't mean aspirin.
明智之选
A wise choice.
甲氧麻黄酮 是不错的选择
Mepheodrone would be a
good investment for you.
是最新的货
It's the newest thing.
我想搞 迷魂药
I was thinking Vertigo.
改良后的那种
Newer thing.
迷魂药市场不景气啊
Tough market,Vertigo.
- 只有一位卖家
- 我知道
- Only one seller.
- I know.
我想请你帮我个忙 安排一次会面
I was hoping you could do me
a favor and arrange a meeting.
他是个异类
He's difficult man.
他不喜欢新朋友
And he does not like new friends.
这是警察掌握到他的信息
This is everything
the police have on him.
告诉他是个见面礼
Tell him it's a gift.
我会尽我所能的
I will see what I can do.
你还得帮我个忙
Provided you do favor for me.
悉听差遣
Vse chto ugodno.
我们组织中很少见到一个美国人
能拥有如此高的低位
It is unusual for an American to hold such
a position of esteem in our organization.
Queen先生
Mr. Queen.
Anatoli Knyazev
Anatoli Knyazev.
对你高度赞扬
He speaks very highly of you.
应该的 我救了他的命
He should. I saved his life.
他做了什么
What did he do?
违背了我的命令
Something I told him not to.
现在可以帮忙了
Now the favor.
替我杀了这人
我就相信你的投资是诚恳的
Kill this man for me,and I will believe
your interest in our organization is genuine.
然后我就会安排你和伯爵见面
And then I will arrange
a meeting with The Count.
- Oliver...
- 闭嘴
- Hey,shut up!
朋友间不必客气
What are friends for?
终于逃出来了 现在什么情况
I'm out of the gates
now. What's going on?
我们是要离开吗
Are we getting out of here?
你带我去哪
Where are you taking me?
虽然这场比赛是一边倒
While I admit that bout
was particularly one-sided,
还有人想来尝试一下吗
would anybody else
like to give it a try?
这次小比试的目的
是加强组织凝聚力
The point of these little gladiatorial
distractions is to strengthen unit cohesion.
为此 我想我们应该给予
To that end,I think our newest recruit
最新招募的成员一次试手的机会
ought to be afforded the
opportunity to try his hand.
难以想象你杀了这个人
I can't believe you
just killed that guy.
你真觉得我就那么点能耐么
You really have a low opinion of me.
哇哦 这个把戏不错
Whoa! That's a neat trick.
什么时候教我
You going to teach me that one day?
- 不教
- 你想干什么
- No.
- What are you doing?
你给这家伙弄个新身份
You need to arrange a
new identity for this guy.
帮他逃出这里
Get him out of the city.
然后俄国佬朋友把伯爵引出来
绿箭侠把他放倒
Right,so your Ruskie pal draws out
The Count,vigilante takes him down.
不 Diggle 那样黑手党
就知道我利用了他们
No,Diggle,because then the Bratva
would know that I used them,
这关系网价值非凡
and that relationship is too valuable.
我得真的亲自见见伯爵
I do the meet with The Count as myself,
让他离开 然后跟踪他到藏身之处
let him leave,then we
follow him to his hideout.
说的真轻松啊
Just that easy,huh?
仍旧需要你的援手
Well,I will still need
my trust bodyguard.
棒极了 真心期待刺激的毒贩生涯
Fantastic. Looking forward to my new
and exciting career as a drug dealer.
他是一名队长
He's a captain.
而且很有钱
And he has money.
你感兴趣吗
Are you interested?
那就...好吧
Let's say...yes.
我爸爸成功的让Brackett法官
放下了强硬立场
My father was able to get Judge
Brackett to back off his hardline stance.
你爸很恨我的
Your father hates me.
- 没有
- No.
我爸爸恨的是他
My father hates him.
- 没有求你参与这事
- 我求了
- Look,nobody asked you to get involved.
- I did.
法官同意判决500小时社区服务
The judge has agreed to a sentence
of 500 hours of community service
缓刑2年
and two years of probation.
临时任命一位代替父母
Provisional on the appointment of
someone to act in loco parentis.
代替什么
In loco what?
法庭我委派一名你的监护人
It means that the court will appoint an
individual to assume responsibility for you.
我
Me.
谢谢你 但你多管闲事了
I say thanks,but no thanks.
Thea
Thea!
你没有别的选择
You don't actually have a choice.
事实上 我有的选
Oh,actually,I do.
我现在18岁了 我可以自己做决定
See,I'm 18 now and I can
make my own decisions.
所以我决定不做你前女友的傀儡
So I decide not to be your
ex-girlfriend's office monkey.
要是你改变主意了
Well,if you change your mind,then.
谢谢
Thank you.
Thea...你知道问题的严重性吗
Thea... You're in real
trouble,and rightly so.
毒驾
Doing drugs and driving?
这荒唐的没边了
Laurel为你争取了很好的判决
It is beyond stupid. That is a
good deal that Laurel got you.
你干吗不接受呢
Why aren't you jumping at it?
我已经有妈妈
I already have a mother.
所以你要去坐牢 这将毁了你的人生
So... you're going to go to jail and
it will ruin the rest of your life.
不
No.
我要毁了妈妈的生活
I want to ruin mom's life.
她是个骗子 还劈腿
She's a liar and a cheat.
承认吧Ollie 你可以假装她是个圣人
I mean,deal with,Ollie. You can pretend
all you want to that she's a saint,
但我恨他 她背叛了爸爸
but I hate her. And she betrayed dad.
所以你去坐牢只是为了报复她
So you're just...you're going
to go to jail to spite her?
Thea... 妈妈没有背叛爸
Thea... Mom didn't cheat on dad.
是爸爸出轨了
He cheated on her.
你就只能编这种程度的故事吗
Is that the best you can come up with?
爸爸并非他自己口中那样
Dad wasn't the man he said he was.
在他死前承认自己辜负了我们
On "The Queen's Gambit" right before he
died,he admitted to me that he failed us.
你 我 还有妈妈
You. Me. And mom.
他并非自己口中那般 他甚至希望...
That he wasn't the man he said
he was and that he just wished...
有更多的时间来纠正他的错误
he wished he had more
time to right his wrongs.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
你信了
Yes,you do.
让我一个人静静
Leave me alone.
你怎么敢
How dare you.
她已经长大了 应该知道真相
She was old enough to know the truth.
Oliver 俄国佬来电话了
Oliver,the Russians called.
会面安排好了
The meet is set.
今晚
It's tonight.
你知道为什么他被称作伯爵吗
You know why they call him The Count?
他研发毒品时 拿流浪汉做实验
When he was developing this drug,he
experimented on the homeless.
妓女 流亡者
Prostitutes,runaways.
警察发现他们的尸体
颈部都有穿孔 就像吸血鬼干得
The police would find their bodies,puncture
marks on their neck,like a vampire.
你不该这么着急见这个人
You should not be in such
a hurry to meet this man.
谢谢你的礼物
Thank you for this.
但是我一点不在乎警察
But I'm not overly
concerned about the SCPD.
我知道你想要参与快感事业
Now,I understand you gentlemen wish to
participate in the feel good business.
- 是的
- 为什么呢
- Yes.
- And why is that?
因为我要开夜店
Well,I am opening a nightclub,
我希望自己顾客享受有一些
额外的玩意
and I'd like my customers to
have a little... something extra.
我也正巧想推广品牌
Well,as it happens,I'm
looking to expand my brand.
好酒的价值在于年份
A good wine's value is
measured by its vintage.
取决于发酵的年数
The number of years it took to ferment.
迷魂药则是靠人命发酵的
Vertigo is measured in lives.
56人死于这种极度的快感
56 people died to perfect this high.
相信我 他们并非死的没有价值
Believe me when I say that
they did not die for nothing.
警察 放下你们的武器
SCPD! Put your weapons down!
放下
Down!
Oliver
Oliver!
没有目击者哦
No witnesses.
从车里出来
Get out of the car!
- 你没事吧
- 拿着它
- You okay?
- Keep it.
我们得走了 小心脚下
Yeah,we got to go. Steps. Let's go.
Oliver
Oliver!
喝了
Drink.
早上好
Mornin'.
感觉如何
How you feeling?
这是我这辈子最糟的宿醉
I feel like I'm getting the
worst hangover of my life.
你这20几岁都在宿醉的人居然说这样的话
That coming from a guy who spent
most of his twenties in a hangover,
看来这感觉是有够糟的
that's really saying something.
能给我解了吗
You think you can uncuff me?
我不会杀了你
Not going to kill you.
我保证
Promise.
你站起来了
You're standing.
恢复的真快啊
That's pretty impressive.
伯爵只给你注射了一半
The Count only got you with half a dose,
你就流了一地的汗
but you still sweated out a
small swimming pool coming down.
伯爵
The Count.
我们的警察朋友抓到了吗
Any chance our friends
in SCPD took him down?
没有 不过我们拿到了这个
None at all,but we
did manage to get this.
可以分析一下
Think we should analyze it.
Oliver 也许你该再休息几个钟头
Listen,Oliver,maybe you
need to give it a few hours.
药量太大 药性没那么快过
A near drug overdose isn't
something you just walk away from.
Thea也一样
Neither is Thea.
怎么回事
What's wrong?
Thea出事了吗
Is everything okay with Thea?
跟你妹没关系 找你呢
This isn't about your
sister,this is about you.
昨晚我们接到线人电话
Last night we got a call from a C.I.,
捣毁了一起大买家和俄国黑帮的交易
busted up a drug sale between a
big time dealer and the Russian mob.
"我们" 你不是负责毒品的吗
"We"? I thought you worked Vice.
联合特遣队 迷魂药的案子调动所有人手
Joint task force. Vertigo's
got everybody holding hands.
如我所说 昨晚的毒品交易砸了
Like I said... Last
night,drug deal gone south.
有目击者看到你也在现场
An eyewitness put you at the scene.
不管是谁 肯定看错了
Whoever he is,he's mistaken.
是吗
Yeah?
我可看到你了 Oliver
I saw you,Oliver.
你真去了吗
Is this true?
我当时在追查"伯爵"
I was checking into The Count.
他可是卖毒品给Thea的人
He's the guy who sold drugs to Thea.
我以为知道他长相后
And I figured if I could
find out what he looked like,
就能给警局素描师些线索
then I could give your sketch
artist something to go on.
我雇了个俄国口音的混混
So I paid a low-life
with a Russian accent
花了大笔钱 安排会面
an obscene amount of
money to arrange a meeting.
然后呢 看清他了吗
And? Did you get eyes on him?
没
No.
你们要起诉我儿子吗
All right,are you pressing
charges against my son?
你若再次涉案 别怪我抓你了
You get involved in this
again,you'll see the inside of a cell,
不会再轻易放过你了
and unlike last time,you
will not see the way out.
警探
Detective.
你帮了Thea 我万分感谢
Thank you for what you did for Thea.
我是给我女儿面子
My daughter asked me
for a favor and I did it.
下不为例了
And that's the end of it.
别觉得我出卖了你
Hope you don't think I sold you out.
不 职责所在
No. Just doing your job.
你究竟在想什么
What on earth were you thinking?
我只是想帮忙
I was trying to help.
跟黑帮毒贩混一起 就算帮忙了吗
By running around with the Russian
mob and a murderous drug dealer?
你疯了吧
Are you out of your mind?!
妈妈 真正令你生气的原因
Mom,look,the real reason
that you're upset is
是我告诉Thea 父亲的真面目吧
because I told Thea the truth about dad.
她无需知道那些
She never needed to know that.
Yes,I did.
妈妈 我长大了 足以面对真相了
I'm old enough to know the truth,Mom.
这无关年龄
It wasn't about your age.
我不想毁了你心中的父亲
It was about preserving
your memory of your father.
他爱你
He loved you.
过错与否 他都是爱你的
No matter his faults,he loved you.
我曾说 真希望死的是你
I said that I wished you
had died instead of him,
可你仍独受委屈 默不作声
but...you still didn't say anything.
为什么这样
Why?
待你有幸能有个女儿 就能理解了
One day,I hope you're lucky enough to
have a daughter,and you'll know why.
抱歉我说的那些话
I'm so sorry for what I said.
我知道的
I know,I know.
现在怎么办
Now what?
如你建议 我们分析迷魂药的成分
Like you said,we analyze the Vertigo.
是液态的 说明有水的成分
It's in liquid form,which
means it contains water.
也许我们可以追根溯源 找到伯爵
So maybe we can trace back to
where in the city The Count is...
制造毒品的地方
cooking up this garbage.
等会
Wait!
我自己来
I'll do it.
去医院看看吧
Hey,we need to get you to a hospital.
不用
No.
Oliver 天知道那药什么成分
Oliver,God knows what was in that drug.
可能会造成永久性伤害
It could be causing permanent damage.
Felicity
Felicity.
他们说你会在这
Hey,they said you'd be up here.
你邋遢得像是被猫拽进来的
You look like something
the cat dragged in.
我不是说楼里真有猫
Not that there are
cats in this building.
确实进来过猫 警卫处理了
Well,once a cat did get
in,but a guard tazed it.
后来整周都有猫毛的味道
It smelled like fur and
static in here for like a week.
你能别靠在窗边吗
Would you mind stepping away
from the window for a moment?
我还没醒酒
I have a little bit of a hangover.
你像是需要一杯血腥玛丽和椒盐卷饼
Sounds like you need a
bloody Mary and a pretzel,
而不是信息技术部
not the I.T. Department.
实际上 我哥们Kevin开了能量饮料公司
Actually,my buddy Kevin is
starting an energy drink company.
他说那对宿醉有很大帮助
He says it's fantastic
for curing hangovers,
可我对进入身体的东西 比较谨慎
but I am very particular about
what it is I put in my body.
看出来了
I've noticed.
不是 我没注意到
I said,not noticed.
对吧
Right?
我想找出配方
I'm trying to find a secret recipe.
你能对样品进行光谱分析吗
Could you please do a
spectroanalysis of the sample
查出哪里它的制造地
and find out exactly where
in the city it's made?
能量饮料干嘛装注射器里
If it's an energy drink,why
is it in a syringe?
我没运动水壶
I ran out of sports bottles.
好吧
Okay.
你编的故事越来越狗血了
Your B.S. stories are getting worse.
我知道
I'm well aware.
Felicity应该分析完了
Looks like Felicity came through.
迷魂药样品里的溶剂
The solvent used in the
Vertigo sample was run off water
源于东贫民窟和海湾交界处的
十个街区范围内的水
originated within a ten block radius
of where East Glades meets the bay.
那除了三年前废弃的少管所
Nothing there except for an
old juvenile detention center
一片荒凉
abandoned about three years ago.
被裁减了
Cutbacks.
可你还是不能去 Oliver
You can't go out there,though,Oliver.
你还受迷魂药的影响
You're still suffering the
after-affects of the Vertigo.
你没听到伯爵说吗
Did you hear The Count?
他要将毒药蔓延至整个城市
He's taking this drug citywide.
现在不阻止 就会成为流行病了
If we don't stop him
now,this becomes an epidemic.
我能阻止你去
I can stop you from leaving.
试试看啊
Try.
Oliver 射中球 就让你去
Oliver,you hit this and you can leave.
想通就好
I'm glad you came to your senses.
记住一件事 Dig
You should always
remember one thing,Dig.
什么
What's that?
我不是非弓箭不可
I don't need the bow.
我的线人说的就是这
My C.I. swears this is the place.
带你的人去侧面
Bring your men up on the flank.
- 好 这边
- 跟上
- Okay,this way.
- Follow me.
- 他来了
- 谁来了
- He's here!
- He who?
帽衫男
The Hood!
看样子 今晚不止我们来啊
Looks like we're not the only guests.
你该待在那堕落的金银窝里
You should have stuck
to your depraved elite.
人们想要 我就提供
I am merely providing
people with what they want.
我才是人民公仆
I am providing a public service!
我也是
So am I.
自食恶果吧
Enjoy the fruits of your labor.
不许动 放下注射器
Freeze! Put down the needle!
否则我就开枪啦
Or I will shoot you!
放下注射器
Put down the syringe.
- 他活该
- 这不是法律允许的
- He deserves this!
- Not according to the law.
人们把你当英雄 包括我女儿
The people that think you're
a hero,people like my daughter,
若看到你现在 就知道你不是英雄了
if they could see you
now... You're no hero.
你就是我常说的 杀手
You're what I always
said you were... a killer.
抓住他
Get him!
叫救护车来 马上
Get me an ambulance. Now!
少年犯来报到了
Juvenile delinquent reporting for duty.
你驾照没了 我五点来接你
Since you lost your driver's
license,I'll pick you up at 5:00.
六点吧 今天工作有点多
6:00. We have a lot
of work for her to do.
那就七点好了 保险
Well,then,let's say
7:00 just to be safe.
现在反悔 会不会太晚了
Is it too late to choose jail?
- 晚了
- 没错
- Yes.
这些文件 你浏览一遍
I need you to go through these files
把07年三月份的文件挑出来
and pull out all the
documents dated March 2007.
你可以的吧
Do you think you could do that?
应该可以
I think I can.
我知道 是我搞砸了
I know I messed up.
你能帮我 万分感谢 Laurel
I really appreciate this,Laurel.
我们会帮你抛开过去的 飞毛腿
We are going to make an upstanding
citizen out of you yet,speedy.
谢谢你 有个榜样在身边
Thank you. And this
will be good for her,
对她来说是好事 你比我强多了
having a role model,somebody
better than me.
你也不错啦
Oh,you're not so bad.
更何况 有她作伴 何尝不是好事呢
And besides,it'll be
nice to have her around.
我接个电话 失陪
I got to take this. Excuse me.
你好
Hello?
我们抓到伯爵了
We got The Count.
拆了他的实验室
掌握了他犯罪所有证据
Bust up his lab,got him on everything
from drug trafficking to homicide.
要关很久了
He'll be gone for a long while.
太好了 谢谢你
That's great,thanks.
见到你真好 Oliver
It was great seeing you,Oliver.
我也是
You,too.
回见
See ya.
他还在危险期
He's still critical.
我从没见过被注射了这么大量的
迷魂药还活下来的人
I've never seen anyone OD on
this much Vertigo and live.
无法想象他大脑和神经系统
There's just no way of knowing
what kind of damage has been done
经受着多大损伤
to his brain and nervous system.
不知道能不能恢复了
Or if its irreparable.
生存...
Shengeun...
活下去
Survive.
谢谢你来见我 去你家我会紧张
Thanks for meeting me. I
was...nervous to come to your house.
好吧...
Okay...
这几周 我在纠结是否告诉你
The thing is,I've been debating whether
or not to share this with you for weeks.
我能相信你吗
Can I trust you?
我不是白痴
I'm not an idiot.
你骗我的故事太扯了
You've dropped some fairly
ridiculous lies on me,
可我还是觉得能相信你
and...yet I still feel
like I can trust you.
怎么会这样
Why is that?
我长了张正直脸呢
I have one of those faces.
抱歉
Sorry.
是的
Yes.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
我有东西给你看
Then I have something to show you.
你之前见过这个吗
Have you ever seen this before?
没
No.
你哪来的
Where'd you get it?
你继父那
From your stepfather.
Walter那里啊
From Walter.
那他是哪来的
Um... Well,where did he get it?
他说是在你家找到的
He said he found it in your house.
是你母亲的东西
That it belongs to your mother.
Walter觉得她有事瞒他
Walter thought she was hiding something.
不止是这些...
Something more,and...
他让我查 自己却消失了
He wanted me to look into
it,but then he vanished.
这东西或许害了Walter
I think this list might
have cost Walter his life.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
绿箭侠
第一季 第十二集 完
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo